geetmanjusha.com 2017-07-19

# Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you are asked to enter your: name, e-mail address. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. **To personalize your experience** \- (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. **To improve our website** \- (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. **To improve customer service** \- (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  4. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  5. **To send periodic emails** \- The email address you provide may be used to send you information in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, You may choose to unfollow or unsubscribe any of the groups or projects that send you email notifications.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in subscription management system, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

We use third-party advertizing networks which may in turn maintain cookies to serve you personalized ad experice. We also use Google Analytics service to learn more about people who are visiting the geetmanjusha.com website. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Notice to Copyright Holders

The website, content and services are provided for personal use only and are not intended to be used for any commercial purpose. No infringement whatsoever is intended. If you hold copyright(s) (or any other proprietary right(s)) to any content, including music lyrics, made available via this website, and have any questions or concerns about the licensing, accuracy, or possible take-down of such content from the website, please contact us at [geetmanjusha facebook page](https://www.facebook.com/Geetmanjusha/) . Any valid complaint or query will be treated sincerely and acted upon as fast as possible.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [geetmanjusha facebook page](https://www.facebook.com/Geetmanjusha/).
